let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Oumuamua?",
    answer: "B. Interstellar Object that passed through the Solar System in 2017",
    options: [
      "A. Massive black hole in Horsehead Nebula",
      "B. Interstellar Object that passed through the Solar System in 2017",
      "C. Comet in the Kuiper Belt",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which Planet has a hexagon at its north pole?",
    answer: "A. Saturn",
    options: ["A. Saturn", "B. Neptune", "C. Venus"],
  },

  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is best described as a 'Luminous Active Galactic Nucleus?",
    answer: "B. Quasar",
    options: ["A. Megatron", "B. Quasar", "C. White Dwarf Star"],
  },

  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "This is the supervoid whose center is approximately 700M light-years from Earth",
    answer: "B. Bootes Void",
    options: ["A. Steppes Void", "B. Bootes Void", "C. Cloggs Void"],
  },

  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The Largest Structure in the observable universe?",
    answer: "A. Hercules-Corona Borealis Great Wall",
    options: ["A. Hercules-Corona Borealis Great Wall", "B. Southern Polar Great Wall", "C. Swift-Gamma Great Wall"],
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The closest extrasolar star to Earth?",
    answer: "A. Proxima Centauri",
    options: ["A. Proxima Centauri", "B. Barnard", "C. Wolf 359"],
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The closest Galaxy to the Milky Way?",
    answer: "B. Andromeda",
    options: ["A. Pinwheel", "B. Andromeda", "C. Whirlpool"],
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The vast cloud of icy planetesimals surrounding the sun?",
    answer: "A. Oort cloud",
    options: ["A. Oort cloud", "B. Reflection nebula", "C. Cosmic ocean"],
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How many galaxies in the observable universe?",
    answer: "C. 2 trillion",
    options: ["A. 500 billion", "B. 1 trillion", "C. 2 trillion"],
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The second most-famous dwarf planet in the solar system?",
    answer: "A. Ceres",
    options: ["A. Ceres", "B. Iris", "C. Loris"],
  },
];
